<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Global Azure Austria 2023</title><link>https://globalazure.at/</link><description>Recent content on Global Azure Austria 2023</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://globalazure.at/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>atwork</title><link>https://globalazure.at/sponsors/atwork/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalazure.at/sponsors/atwork/</guid><description>atwork develops business solutions to meet the growing application of Internet technologies in business processes, including Microsoft 365 and Microsoft Azure. We specialize in consulting and developing lines of business apps, cloud computing workloads and web solutions. The atwork team is a reliable and competent partner for the implementation of IT solutions. We are always looking for new colleagues to help us support our customers in cloud technologies! We are always looking for new dedicated colleagues to help us support our customers in cloud technologies!</description></item><item><title>Call for Participation</title><link>https://globalazure.at/call-for-participation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalazure.at/call-for-participation/</guid><description>Call for Participation We are currently preparing the session content for Global Azure Austria 2023.
Global Azure is from the community, for the community. This is where you come in, dear speakers. GAA would not be possible without your great content and dedication. This year&amp;rsquo;s topic is:
Cloud Computing - What&amp;rsquo;s next?
We have chosen this motto because cloud computing has become the new normal in the last few years. Now we want to explore the near to mid-term future of cloud computing, particularly the Microsoft Azure cloud.</description></item><item><title>Code of Conduct</title><link>https://globalazure.at/code-of-conduct/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalazure.at/code-of-conduct/</guid><description>Code of Conduct Global Azure Austria uses the Berlin Code of Conduct.
Purpose Our goal is to be inclusive to the largest number of contributors, with the most varied and diverse backgrounds possible. As such, we are committed to providing a friendly, safe and welcoming environment for all, regardless of gender, sexual orientation, ability, ethnicity, socioeconomic status and religion (or lack thereof).
This Code of Conduct outlines our expectations for all those who participate in our community, as well as the consequences for unacceptable behavior.</description></item><item><title>Coding Club Linz e.V.</title><link>https://globalazure.at/sponsors/coding-club-linz/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalazure.at/sponsors/coding-club-linz/</guid><description>Der Coding Club Linz e.V. ist ein gemeinnütziger Verein mit dem Ziel, die Kenntnisse der Allgemeinheit über Computer im Allgemeinen und Softwareentwicklung im Speziellen zu fördern. Der Verein ist unter anderem Trägerorganisation des CoderDojo Linz, einem kostenlosen Programmierclub für Kinder und Jugendliche. Neben dem CoderDojo veranstaltet der Coding Club Linz regelmäßig kostenlose Konferenzen und Meetups wie zum Beispiel das jährliche Global Azure Austria-Event sowie das Rust Meetup Linz.
Coding Club Linz e.</description></item><item><title>cubido</title><link>https://globalazure.at/sponsors/cubido/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalazure.at/sponsors/cubido/</guid><description>Wir kombinieren jahrelange Erfahrung mit neuen, innovativen Ideen. Seit 15 Jahren sind wir erfolgreich für mittlere und große Unternehmen im deutschsprachigen Raum in den Bereichen Analytics und Development tätig.
Im Bereich Development setzen wir auf die Entwicklung von individuellen, hochspezialisierten Lösungen. Hierzu werden erprobte Standardkomponenten um projektspezifische Funktionen erweitert, sodass am Ende eine Lösung entsteht, die sich an den Unternehmensprozess des Kunden anpasst und nicht umgekehrt. So werden höchste Benutzerfreundlichkeit und eine nahtlose Anbindung an vorhandene Systeme gewährleistet.</description></item><item><title>Dynatrace</title><link>https://globalazure.at/sponsors/dynatrace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalazure.at/sponsors/dynatrace/</guid><description>Founded in 2005 in Linz, Austria, Dynatrace is the world market leader in software intelligence. On the way to the autonomous, self-healing, and self-protecting cloud, Dynatrace supports the largest companies in the world with AI-driven, answer-based automation to create perfect digital solutions. Millions of people benefit from this in the age of digitalization: when banking, traveling, shopping, working on the go, or in the health sector. The technological and creative heart of software development at Dynatrace beats in Europe: Linz is the company’s global engineering headquarters with additional engineering locations in Hagenberg, Graz, Klagenfurt, Vienna, Innsbruck, Barcelona, Gdansk, Tallinn, and Detroit.</description></item><item><title>Microsoft</title><link>https://globalazure.at/sponsors/microsoft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalazure.at/sponsors/microsoft/</guid><description>Microsoft ist das führende Unternehmen für Plattformen und Produktivität für die “mobile first, cloud first”-Welt.
Seit 1991 ist Microsoft mit einer Niederlassung in Wien vertreten und beschäftigt rund 330 Mitarbeiter*innen. Das Ziel ist, gemeinsam mit mehr als 4.000 heimischen Partnerunternehmen, Menschen und Unternehmen zu ermöglichen, durch Software ihr volles Potenzial auszuschöpfen.
Mit der Ankündigung des ersten Rechenzentrums in Österreich baut Microsoft seine Cloud-Region weiter aus und fördert damit Innovation und Wachstum.</description></item><item><title>ppedv AG</title><link>https://globalazure.at/sponsors/ppedv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalazure.at/sponsors/ppedv/</guid><description>Wir stehen bereits seit 1997 für qualifizierte Weiterbildung rund um das Thema IT. Wir bieten 100+ Kurse für Anwender, Entwickler und Administratoren an – vom Einsteiger bis zum Profi – in Voll- und Teilzeit (halbtags). Nehmen Sie in einem unserer 4 Schulungszentren (Berlin, München, Burghausen, Wien) oder von überall im etablierten Virtual Classroom teil. Gerne kommen wir für größere ITProjekte oder maßgeschneiderte Trainings auch zu Ihnen ins Unternehmen. Mit praxisnahen Schulungen unterstützen wir unsere Kunden dabei, Wissenslücken zu schließen und Gelerntes in der Praxis umzusetzen.</description></item><item><title>Sessions</title><link>https://globalazure.at/sessions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalazure.at/sessions/</guid><description>
# Sessions</description></item><item><title>Speakers</title><link>https://globalazure.at/speakers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalazure.at/speakers/</guid><description>
# Speakers</description></item><item><title>Sponsors</title><link>https://globalazure.at/sponsor-packs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalazure.at/sponsor-packs/</guid><description>Sponsor Packs Global Azure Austria is a community event. It is 100% free for everybody. However, even a free, virtual event costs money. Therefore, we are looking for sponsors who help us covering the costs. Collected sponsor fees that exceed the costs of GAA 2023 are used for financing CoderDojo Linz, our free, volunteer-driven programming club for kids.
Book Sponsor Pack Main Platinum Sponsor GAA has a single, Platinum sponsor and we want to say a huge thank you to Microsoft for taking this spot!</description></item><item><title>Sprecher Automation</title><link>https://globalazure.at/sponsors/sprecher/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalazure.at/sponsors/sprecher/</guid><description>Sprecher Automation ist Hersteller und Anbieter von Produkten und Lösungen für Energieversorgung und Prozessautomatisierung. Wir machen kritische Infrastrukturen sicherer und optimieren komplexe Energie- und Industrieprozesse. Unsere Kundinnen und Kunden aus den Bereichen Energieversorgung, Industrie und Infrastruktur erwarten höchstes Niveau punkto Qualität, Verfügbarkeit und Sicherheit – Ansprüche, die wir natürlich auch an uns selbst stellen.
Unsere Mitarbeiter:innen sind die Basis unseres Erfolgs. Sie entwickeln, produzieren, montieren und bedienen Lösungen und Produkte für die Anlagen unserer (inter-)nationalen Kunden.</description></item><item><title>Streaming</title><link>https://globalazure.at/streaming/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalazure.at/streaming/</guid><description>Watch Sessions of Global Azure Austria Global Azure Austria 2023 will happen in gather.town. Detailed instructions for how to join will be provided a few days before the event.
We invite everybody to join us in gather.town for optimal event experience. However, if you do not want to use this platform, we will provide direkt streaming links for all sessions, too. The streaming links will be published a few days before the event.</description></item><item><title>time cockpit</title><link>https://globalazure.at/sponsors/timecockpit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalazure.at/sponsors/timecockpit/</guid><description>Time cockpit ist eine Projektzeiterfassung für Knowledge Worker. Grafischer Zeitbuchungskalender, automatische Tätigkeitsaufzeichnung über Signal Tracker, umfassende Erweiterbarkeit und Anpassbarkeit inkl. Web APIs, volle Offlinefähigkeit und einfachste Verwendung durch SaaS machen es zur optimalen Lösung speziell im IT-Umfeld.
software architects gmbh
Kornstraße 7A
A-4060 Leonding
www.timecockpit.com</description></item><item><title>Zühlke - Empowering Ideas</title><link>https://globalazure.at/sponsors/zuehlke/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalazure.at/sponsors/zuehlke/</guid><description>Wir sind überzeugt, dass Innovationen und technologischer Fortschritt unsere Wirtschaft und Gesellschaft positiv verändern können. Gemeinsam mit unseren Kunden arbeiten wir tagtäglich an nachhaltigen Lösungen für die Zukunft.
Zühlke ist ein weltweit tätiger Innovationsdienstleister. Wir kreieren neue Ideen und Geschäftsmodelle für unsere Kunden. Auf Basis neuester Technologien erschaffen und transformieren wir Dienstleistungen und Produkte – von der initialen Vision über die Entwicklung, die Produktion und die Auslieferung bis hin zum Betrieb.</description></item></channel></rss>